BB84 Roadmap

1. Simple BB84 working
    Set up random bit generation, random basis generation, sifting and QBER
    Plot QBER against N (number of qubits)

2. Add Eve 
    Evedrops on each qubit and measures with a random basis, then sends to Bob
    Now plot QBER with Eve present (should go to 25%)

3. Add Noise
    Add noise innit (idk how)

4. Write up a lil report
    Make it look good innit